

About Me

Career Goal: Earning Respect and Making a Positive Contribution I am driven by my skills, dedication and hard work to attain a position that not only commands respect for my knowledge, but also allows me to make a tangible difference to the organization. I am seeking a challenging role that will provide me with opportunities to expand my knowledge and achieve my personal and professional goals.



+91 8329523743



janhavic2499@gmail.com



Nashik, Maharashtra

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

EXPERTISE & SKILLS

- Management Skills
- Business Development
- Creativity
- Social Media Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Team Management

CHAUDHARI

Business Development (International & Domestic) **IMMEDIATE JOINER**

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

Senior Business Development Executive Ellora Infotech Pvt Ltd April 2023 - Dec 2023 (9 months)

Purely B2B Business Development, Managing Team of 10 Marketers, International Business Development, Email Marketing, Cold Calling

Social Media Marketing Manager AES Weblearn

Jun 2022 - Nov 2022 · (6 months)

Working as a Social Media Manager, posting creatives daily on social media like Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn

Social Media Specialist DESIGN WAREHOUSE LIMITED Jul 2021 - Dec 2021 · (6 months)

Handling clients calls, Clients meeting and Appointment Generation.

EDUCATION

BYK college of commerce

Bachelor of Commerce - B.com, Accounting and Business Management Jun 2018 - Oct 2020

DY Patil University

Junior college, Commerce Jun 2015 - Mar 2017

COURSES

Frankfinn Institute of Air Hostess Training

Air Hostess Training Jun 2022 - Nov 2022

EXPERIENCE DETAILS

Senior Business Development Executive Ellora Infotech Pvt Ltd

Roles & Responsibilities:

- 1. Appointment Generation (B2B) for the client's of Ellora Infotech Pvt Ltd into IT segment for India, USA, UK & Europe
- 2. Generating Enquiries (B2B) for Parent Company Ellora EPC Pvt Ltd for Industrial Construction for India Region
- 3. Team Management (Team of 10 Tele-callers for various projects of Ellora Infotech Pvt Ltd
- 4. Recruitment (For various profiles of Ellora Group as a whole
- 5. Client Management (Day to Day client reporting and keeping them up to date on the marketing projects they outsourced
- 6. Other Marketing Activities such as Data Procurement, Creating Marketing Collaterals, Managing Ellora Events, etc.

Performance:

- 1. For Ellora Infotech Pvt Ltd, I used to generate around 20 appointments per month through channels such as LinkedIn approach, Email Marketing, Cold Calling, etc. Out of 20 appointments scheduled, 15 used to get successful/qualified
- 2. For Ellora EPC Pvt Ltd, I used to perform various marketing to generate inquiries for Industrial construction. The average inquiry value was between INR 1 Cr to 15 Cr. I was able to generate 10 inquiries / Request for Quotations with a total valuation of INR 26.8 Cr within just a span of 2 months.
- 3. Managing a team of 10 tele-callers for generating visitor registrations for B2B events of Informa Markets. Was responsible for generating 3k to 4k leads per month from the entire team. Preparing Reports, and maintaining attendance, Solving their queries, etc.
- 4. Was also responsible for recruitment for a brief time to fulfill the hiring requirements. Was able to onboard 7 candidates for several positions across Ellora Group within a time span of 2 months while working on it intermittently.
- 5. Used to coordinate with the respective client for updates, daily reporting and other day to day communication for the various projects assigned to me for events.
- 6. Used to Manage Ellora EPC Event coordination and Creating social media posts, creating company Profiles for new ventures of Ellora such as Ellora Work Spaces and Ellora Logistics Parks, etc. Successfully coordinated Professional Premier League (PPL) at Nashik where Ellora was a title sponsor. I used to make all the arrangements for branding and other required support in order to reach a bigger audience for the awareness purpose.

Reason for Leaving: Salary Issues, Toxic Work Environment, Lack of Growth Opportunities for Female Employees

Social Media Manager AES Weblearn Pvt Ltd

Roles & Responsibilities:

- 1. Social Media Strategy for B2C customers
- 2. Infographic Creation on Canva
- 3. Paid Advertisement Campaigns on Social Media
- 4. Lead Generation and lead management for these campaigns

Performance:

- 1. For AES Weblearn I used to create a social media strategy in order to increase followers and bring awareness within the target audience. Our target audience was students based in India looking for skills certifications for multiple courses
- 2. Create appealing infographics, reels, stories, videos, etc. posts on canva which will a greater impact to the audience and posting it on social media sites such as Facebook and Instagram. I used to post it daily on these platforms. I was able to increase more than 3k followers for the company page on social media in the span of 6 months.
- 3. Creating paid social media campaigns, optimizations for the same. Making sure the campaigns run smoothly and reduce the spam leads ratio in order to get maximum qualified output from the campaigns
- 4. Generated around 300 to 500 qualified leads a months from social media campaigns in order to reach the target.

Reason for Leaving: Limited growth opportunities in the respected field within this organization.

Business Development Executive Design Warehouse Pvt Ltd

Roles & Responsibilities:

- 1. Lead Generation and Appointment Generation.
- 2. Social Media Management.
- 3. Sales and Deal Closure.

Performance:

- 1. For Design Warehouse I used to generate leads for for their marketing services for Maharashtra Location. Used to generate 2 to 3 leads on a daily basis.
- 2. Create social media strategy and creating infographics on canva to be posted on social media channels
- 3. Once the leads were generated I used to send a proposal for our services and meet with the clients face to face to close the deals. I was responsible for generating a revenue of recurring revenue of INR 1.5 lacs per month.

Reason for Leaving: Due to personal reasons I had to leave this job.

WHY SHOULD YOU HIRE ME

- I have a business development experience for both B2B and B2C Customer Base.
- Experience of handling a high ticket size deals, talking to high level decision makers such as C-Level Prospects.
- Have a versatile experience in multiple industry and service industry.
- · Out of the box thinking. I have always been a smart worker and finding simpler ways to get the work done
- I am able to create a cheerful and healthy work environment in and around me which has led to increased productivity of the team
- Experience of managing a team and able to train new people
- Also has a brief experience into recruitment which comes in handy

SOFTWARES AND TOOLS

| Name of the Tool | Beginner | Proficient | Expert |
|-------------------------------|----------|-------------------------|-------------------------|
| LinkedIn Sales Navigator | | | $\overline{\checkmark}$ |
| Slintel for Mobile Numbers | | | \checkmark |
| Apollo.io for Email Addresses | | | $\overline{\checkmark}$ |
| Canva for graphic Designing | | | \checkmark |
| Naukri Portal for Recruitment | | | \checkmark |
| Indeed for Recruitment | | | $\overline{\checkmark}$ |
| Creator Studio | | $\overline{\checkmark}$ | |
| Zoominfo | | left | |

All the above mentioned information is true to my knowledge